Friends welcome back
in this video you will get to know brother
what is the claim procedure and brother my
scooter was crushed so we are going to
give it in the claim and we are going to the
service center and brother after going there we will find out
what all the procedures are going to be
and brother in how many days will I get my scooter
and today the date is
10th and it is 10th July brother and the
time is 1:56 so right now we have gone straight to
our service center and go there and see
what all the scenes are going to be and I will
tell you the full procedure what has to be done
and I will also tell you that my scooter is damaged
and if you are new to this channel then
brother subscribe and like the video
and brother you should watch my crush video,
you will get to know how my
scooter was crushed so
go and check it out and then
in the clamp procedure I will tell you what claim is going to be taken
and how we will take the claim stay tuned
in the video and
keep supporting the video  Give it a like and subscribe to the channel so
gas has finally entered your
service center and asks
hey the scooter was crushed the scooter was crushed
so I had to
give the scooter for the claim it must be Mukesh let's
talk to Mukesh there is
company
insurance
in the car right now I will have to go down the drain he must be there I can
tell you he will
fix it as it is required ok I won't know it
means it is
broken look at this one and it is
shaking completely from here and right now it is saying that it will take
10 to 12 days and look at this also we will get this
changed and look here also it is
completely scratched and this panel is
completely scratched from here this one
also and this one is also scratched
but brother I don't know
which parties it is, they will change it
because they said that the
brother who will come to do the survey he told
what all will be included so brother I won't know right now
but right now let's go to fill the cream form
and I have signed the documents
and right now bhaiya had
finalized his details and he
said from 12  It will come in 15 days and brother,
we will have to wait for 12 to 15 days and now we will
go straight home from here and brother, whatever
process was there, it was an easy process, all you have to do is take
your documents
which are Aadhar card, PAN card and
driving license, you have to take that thing
and after getting each form filed
brother, they will get one or two signatures and after that
brother, brother, they will tell you to come after 12 to 15
days,
so I have already taken the scooter
from the service center people brother and brother, how did they even find out for
so many days that
brother, we got the scooter after 12 days,
I had given it after 12 days on 10th July and
we got the scooter on 22nd July and the
reason for me was that brother, these parts
come to Banda first for survey, then they ask for these parts, so it takes
a week or two
in the procedure, that is why it got
delayed and I have to stop the story
and then tell you brother what all changes have happened
in this scooter and  Which
new parts have been added and what pricing has come
brother, it is prevalent here, we put the scooter here,
first we turn it off,
put it on the double stand, then I will tell you
brother what all is there, see first of all let me show you the
look,
check the look,
brother, he has given this scooter, look, it is looking great, is
n't it complete,
brother, he has given the scooter after complete 12 days, so
now I will tell you what all things have been added,
brother, first of all this has been added
because there was a scratch here, so this one has been
added, this one also, this one also
means it is completely touched, this will change, so this will
also change and this one has changed
and this is different and this thing is
different, so this has also changed because it had
fallen from here, so this one and this
one has become single, this is called bumper
of something, so brother, this one is the first one here, the
left one has changed, this and
your headlight has also changed, your headlight has also
changed, the front one which was completely
broken brother  And this one has also changed
because it was also shaking a little from here,
so this one was also completely broken, there were
no scratches on it but it was broken,
so this one has also changed, this
part of mine has not changed and this one has also changed and the change that has happened is
this
lever of ours has changed and this whole one below
because it had completely fallen and the stand had also
changed because the stand had also fallen
and this foot race
which seems to be this one and this one is actually
written on the top,
right now this thing has been paneered, this one has been changed, this one, this one and this one has
completely changed from here, but they have
not changed this, I don't know why they have not changed it, the
brother who came for the survey did
not say that this will be changed or maybe he might have missed it, so
brother,
I can blame the company people for this, I can
blame the surveyor as well, but no problem, we will
paint it a little bit, if there is
more need, then we will change it from outside,
but right now it works like this, there is no
problem and the rest I will show it in water, I will paint a little in
front of you,
see this
TVS racing one has also been painted  This is also
small, it gives a
nice look brother, the one who will take it out and give it to you, the whole thing has been
changed, the
entire scooter will be unboxed,
new parts were fitted and I also told you what to do,
now let's come to its pricing brother, the
price they have made, I will
show you the bill, I had taken a photo of
which parts have changed and for how much, let's keep it, we do
n't put it in the bag, we do
n't keep it, we will put it later, then
I will tell you the prices, so
brother, first of all let's come to the Billion Food Pack Leg
Pe Peel Food Food Wala, here it is brother, the player
foot, its pricing is 173 rupees,
173 and the one which is in ours, which is the
LED headlight, brother, the front LED
headlight, its pricing is 3851,
3000, 851, its pricing is 3851, this headlight
of ours was completely damaged from inside, it was completely
damaged from inside, so they have
changed the whole headlight and our lever is for
450, this one, this one, the lever is for 450
and now the correct lever is there
Blue is visible, so its price is
Deep Denim Blue, which is the price of this,
its approximate price is 1100 rupees,
1100 is the price of this complete part
and both the parts of this side have changed, the
upper one has also changed and the lower one has
also changed, its price is
₹1690 means 1700 rupees, take 1700,
show its price and both of these together
and 1100 for single, 1100 for the upper one
and the rest is ₹200, our indicator,
this one, this change is of ₹200, its
pricing has come, it is 350, the one with
new color is ₹350 and this thing is
written on the ji, TVS Racing, its
cost has come,
so what is its total gas bill, its total parts
bill,
15000 has
come, 15675 brother,
its price is 15675 and brother, the
insurance which I had taken, they have passed it, which is
15251  Out of this, there was 1570,
I will tell you now, yes it
was 15675, from that if we subtract this one
which is our bill passed
15251, then there will be a
difference of approx 430, they say that brother,
we have to pay 430 for gas also and 100 was
our file charge, for whatever claim is made, the
company which we go to, takes 100
for file charge, so 100 plus
430 and the total became 530, so brother, we had to pay 530 rupees for the
scooter to the company
and the rest, brother, it was
in insurance, hence it has been repaired, it is
looking very good and if brother it was
not in insurance, then brother,
you know the price, whatever the total bill would have been,
brother, if it had gone to me, it would have been
15000, it was on one side,
hence the tax and right now it is standing in front of us, I will give it to you,
Next Android
Chittorgarh  Let's go straight and tell
you some things, you have already come on the scooter after sitting on it and I am here, I will
tell you brother, the process was
very simple, brother, if
your scooter or bike gets into an accident and gets damaged, then you do
n't have to do anything, if it is in insurance, then
you have to directly go and park it at the service center
and say that it has been damaged,
and but keep one thing in mind brother, the person who is repairing your
scooter should have a
license, it should be a valid
license, whenever the insurance
company gives a claim, if the person who is repairing the
scooter, scooter or bike gets into an
accident, then
brother the company does not give the insurance claim, so
brother, keep this thing in mind and
I have clarified this thing to you, and there is no other
issue, it just takes a little time,
our scooter lost 12 days
because brother, this is a new model and it is the
latest model of Toc and Toc so its
parts were available, that is why
they took more time and
if you  Is it a scooter or is it a red colour
race edition, so brother, who knows, the part might be
available in it and we can give you the scooter soon,
within a week, I liked the
service very much but it got a little late, so no
problem, right now we are going straight home from here
and brother, if you found this video informative, then
like the video, share it and
subscribe and right now we are going straight
home and will meet you in the next video, till then
bye and take care